Death is for the living and not for the dead so much.
Gates of Heaven is a documentary film directed by Errol Morris.
A documentary about a pet cemetery in California, and
the people who have pets buried there.
Herself, played by Lucille Billingsley.
Herself, played by Zella Graham.
Himself, played by Cal Harberts.
Himself, played by Dan Harberts.
Himself, played by Phil Harberts.
Himself, played by Scottie Harberts.
Gates of Heaven is a 1978 American independent documentary film produced,
directed, and edited by Errol Morris about the pet cemetery business.
It was made when Morris was unknown and did much to launch his career.
The film explores themes of pet, pet cemetery, napa valley.